[Music]
you know it's the simple it's the little
things that we do in life or in business
that build trust with somebody you know
showing up when you say you're going to
show up doing the things that you say
you're going to do and consistently
doing them we're not looking for a here
today gone tomorrow type of relationship
i know very well that if i'm gonna have
a long-term thriving business it's
because my clients are still my clients
so i'm all about providing service and
consultation on an ongoing basis so i
can maintain that relationship and
continue to grow my business over time
[Music]
all the people that i deal with they
know who i am
it's not a see me here and never see me
again and see me here and see me again
tomorrow
they need to feel that our phone is
always there you know the line is always
open
they can approach us we can approach
them
and it is a good working relationship in
both directions
to know that the door is open
our clients can expect that
you